https://www.batescorp.com/privacy-notice

We use cookies to make your experience better. To comply with the new e-Privacy directive, we need to ask for your consent to set the cookies.
Privacy Notice
Bates Corporation Online Store knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Bates Corporation Online Store, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does Bates Corporation Online Store Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Bates Corporation Online Store. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us:
We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
Automatic Information:
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Bates Corporation Online Store. Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of the information we receive. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Bates Corporation Online Store if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.
E-mail Communications:
To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Bates Corporation Online Store if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this by selecting unsubscribed in the newsletters menu.
What About Cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as automatic login and permanent shopping carts for storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Bates Corporation Online Store's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Does Bates Corporation Online Store Share the Information It Receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We do not share customer information with anyone.
Promotional Offers:
Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Bates Corporation Online Store customers. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your account newsletter preference as that is how we will send out our promotions.
Business Transfers:
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Bates Corporation Online Store, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
Protection of Bates Corporation Online Store and Others:
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Bates Corporation Online Store, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
With Your Consent:
Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
What Information Can I Access?
Bates Corporation Online Store gives you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.
Your Account
What Choices Do I Have?
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such Bates Corporation Online Store features as Automatic login, and permanent shopping carts. You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "My Account" pages. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this in the newsletter menu.
Children
Bates Corporation Online Store does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use Bates Corporation Online Store only with involvement of a parent or guardian.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit Bates Corporation Online Store, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Indiana. If you have any concern about privacy at Bates Corporation Online Store, please send us a thorough description to batescorp@batecorp.com, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
Information You Give Us
You provide most such information when you search, buy, bid, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; make an order or an Auction bid; provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us); communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; by providing employer, school, or other such information; participate in Discussion Boards; provide and rate Reviews. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone number; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including address and phone number; other people; content of reviews and e-mails to us; and financial information, including Social Security and driver's license numbers.
Automatic Information
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; and products you viewed or searched for.
CATEGORIES
Air CleanerAir CleanerCapFilterPipes, Stacks, TubesAir ConditionerCondenserConversion KitCompressorDryerEvaporatorLineSwitchValvesAttachmentsBelt PulleyMowerBrake PartsBrake ActuatorBrake BandsBrake DiscBrake DrumBrake PlateBushings, Pins, ETC.HousingLineLinkageMaster CylinderPedalShaftsSpringCab PartsTool TrayCab Door, PartsFan AssemblyFilterFloor MatHandlesHeaterInterior KitMirrorsMountPanelPlatformStepsWindowsClutchSlave CylinderBushings, Pins, ETC.Clutch BearingClutch BoosterClutch BrakeClutch DiscClutch KitClutch ToolCoverDrive PlateForkGasket SetHousingLinkageMaster CylinderPedalPressure PlateShaftsSpringTA PartsControlsBracketBrake ActuatorCableCarburetorCoverForkGear ShiftGovernorHandlesHousingHydro PartsLeverLinkagePark LockPedalPTO LinkageRange ShiftRodShaftsSpringStarterTA PartsTel-A-DepthThrottleValvesCoolingPulleyFanGasket SetHosesOil CoolerPipes, Stacks, TubesRadiatorRadiator CapThermostatWater PumpElectricalAlternatorBattery BoxBattery CoverBattery TrayCharging SystemDistributorDistributor PartsDistributor Parts DelcoDistributor Parts PrestoliteFuseGaugesGeneratorGlow PlugHornIgnitonLight BracketLightsMagneto PartsRadioRegulatorStarterSwitchTest EquipmentWiring HarnessEngineBalancerBeltsBlock HeaterBreatherBushings, Pins, ETC.Cam BearingsCamshaftConnecting RodCoolerCoverCrankcaseCrankshaftCylinderCylinder HeadFilterFlywheelGasket SetGaugesGearsGovernorHand CrankMain BearingsMountsOil CoolerOil FilterOil PanOil PumpOverhaul KitPiston, RingsPreCupPulleyRing GearRod BearingsStudValve TrainExhaustGasket SetManifoldMufflerPipes, Stacks, TubesTurbochargerFront AxleShaftAxleBearingsBolsterBushings, Pins, ETC.MFWD AxleMountSpindleStay RodSteering ArmSteering KnuckleSupportTie RodsWheel HubFuelBracketCableCarburetorCarburetor KitsCarburetor PartsFilterFloatGaugesInjection PumpInjectorsLinePumpSediment BowlSolenoidTankHitchBushings, Pins, ETC.DrawbarFast Hitch AdaptersLift LinkageLinkageRockshaftSpringSupportSway LimiterTop LinkBushingsRodTorque TubeValvesHydraulicsAccumulatorBracketBushings, Pins, ETC.CoolerCouplersCoverCylinderDipstickDraft PumpFilterGasket SetGearsHandlesHosesHousingHydro PartsLeverLinkageManifoldPipes, Stacks, TubesPumpRockshaftShaftsSpringSteering PumpTel-A-DepthTouch ControlValvesInstrumentsGearsBracketBushings, Pins, ETC.GaugesLightsPanelSupportSwitchTachometerTachometer CableTachometer DriveOperators StationBracketCoverFendersHandlesMiscPanelPlatformStepsToolboxProduct GraphicsDecalsDecal SetsEmblemsMisc DecalsSerial Number TagPTOComplete AssemblyPressure PlateBearingsBrake BandsBeltsBrake DrumBracketBreatherBushings, Pins, ETC.Clutch BearingClutch DiscClutch KitClutch PlateConversion KitGasket SetGearsHousingIPTO ShaftLeverLinkagePTO LinkagePTO ShieldPulleyRetainersShaftsPublicationsManualsRear AxleBushings, Pins, ETC.Axle ShaftsBearingsBoltsCarrierCapDifferentialFinal DriveGasket SetGearsHousingWheel HubSeatBeltsBoltsBracketBushings, Pins, ETC.FastenersSeat SupportSeatsSpringSuspensionSheet Metal & GrillesTankCoverFan AssemblyFastenersFendersGrilleHoodHousingPanelSupportToolboxSteeringLineSteering ArmSteering KnuckleBearingsBushings, Pins, ETC.Char-Lynn Power SteeringCylinderFront AxleGearsHousingLinkagePipes, Stacks, TubesShaftsSpindleStay RodSteering BoxSteering Clutch DiscsSteering Hand PumpSteering WheelSupportValvesTransmissionBracketClutch BoosterAxle ShaftsBearingsBushings, Pins, ETC.ControlsCountershaftCouplersCoverDifferentialFinal DriveFlywheelForkGasket SetGear ShiftGearsHousingHydrostatLeverLineLinkagePulleyRear AxleRetainersRing GearShaftsSupportTA AssembliesTA Gasket SetTA PartsTransfer CaseValvesWheelsBearingsBoltsBushings, Pins, ETC.ClampsDual HubFastenersRimsWedgesWheel Center CastWheel HubWheel WeightWeightsWeight BracketWheelsApparel, Books, & CollectablesCoffee TableHatsTractor MacFlags3x5SignsLights
Information
Conditions of Use
Contact us
Tax Exempt Forms
Our Location
Privacy Notice
Request Brochure
Salvage Tractors
